<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gip Site</title>
    <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gip Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 15:14:32 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Tâche 4: FAQ ~ Youtube</title>
      <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak4-FAQ/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 15:14:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak4-FAQ/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;où-puis-je-trouver-mes-vidéos-préférées:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;Où puis-je trouver mes vidéos préférées?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;dans votre menu à gauche, cliquez sur la playlist “Favorites”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;si-vous-faites-une-playlist-sur-un-ordinateur-comment-est-ce-que-je-vois-cette-playlist-sur-une-autre-playlist:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;Si vous faites une playlist sur un ordinateur, Comment est-ce que je vois cette playlist sur une autre playlist?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vous voyez la playlist quand vous connectez avec votre account de Google&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;comment-puis-je-supprimer-toute-une-playlist:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;Comment puis-je supprimer toute une playlist?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vous devez selectionner la playlist que vous voulez supprimer, au droit vous pouvez selectionner l’option: “ Supprimer la playlist”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;quand-je-selectionner-un-video-le-video-ne-marche-pas-comment-est-ce-que-je-le-vois-maintenant:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;Quand je selectionner un video, le video ne marche pas. comment est-ce que je le vois  maintenant?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressez sur f5 à votre clavier
Redémarrez votre ordinateur
Essayez avec un autre navigateur
Mettez à jour votre navigateur&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;il-y-a-encore-d-autre-site-comme-youtube:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;Il y a encore d’autre site comme youtube?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vimeo.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dailymotion.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veoh.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;j-ai-entendu-que-c-est-possible-de-faire-de-l-argent-sur-youtube-comment-ça-marche:1dcf0bc48922d046d371bd1e4d98dd4d&#34;&gt;J’ai entendu que c’est possible de faire de l’argent sur youtube, comment ça marche?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vous créez un  chaïne sur youtube&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vous commencez de faire un video&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vous téléchargez la vidéo que vous avez créé&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vous activez les annonces&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;quand les voyeurs de votre video, regarde aux annonces, vous gangez de l’argent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Task 5: Autobiography</title>
      <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak5-Autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 15:14:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak5-Autobiography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h3 id=&#34;autobiography-gip-task-05:344c64788bb5fb907d7294b8bb012b72&#34;&gt;Autobiography : GIP TASK 05&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
My name is Mario Van Kerckhoven, some people refer to me as : “ the spiritmaster of Aftermath”, since im the only spiritmaster in the clan Aftermath . I am 16 years old and live in Zandhoven, Belgium. I am still going to the school which is called ‘Immacullata’. It is situated in Oostmalle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
My first expierence with IT obviously was gaming, I think i was 5 or 6 years old when my parents bought me a playstation 2, which was awesome back in the days. When i started to buy my first games, I mean my parents, i tought the characters looked a lot like real people and i tried things in real life that i saw in one of the games i had been playing. I also played on the PC since some of my friends told me to visit websites like Speeleiland.be and funnygames.be .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
At the moment IT means for me going to school and follow lessons like software and system management. That also causes that when I am at home, I am sometimes doing IT related things like changing the name of the router. Each week im on the computer for an average of 4-6 hours a day, school included. My IT-related achievements at the moment are: finding a job ( Sita helpdesk support Beerse), I am the number 1 gamer on a minecraft server and I passed 1 year of IT-management on Immacullata. The fascinating part of the IT-related stuff is that u are always puzzling to change nothing in something. As u are following IT-related website/pages on the internet u can clearly see how the  world in changing because of IT-related things like the internet and games. I wouldn’t see myself in an expert yet, but each day i learn more and without noticing I am sure i will become an expert.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
When I look to the future I see myself working as a guy from the IT department and maybe a website builder as secondary occupation to make some more money. This could become my major activity as I notice a lot of enterprises ask for a website. At the moment i am already testing if that is somehow possible by a task for school. We have to make a business plan for business management. So i deceided to make it about making websites for people.
one of my aspirations is to one day make some sort of social network that is even better then Facebook and Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
I personally think my PC and I are connected because all important data I have is on my computer or in the cloud so I can acces it from my smartphone. IT has quiet an important impact on my life and as I am following IT management I think that impact can only grow bigger and bigger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/xSprfRA.png&#34; alt=&#34;Doing IT things&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taak 1: IT-tapa: Youtube</title>
      <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak1-%20IT-tapa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 00:14:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/gip/Taak1-%20IT-tapa/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;in afwachting tot publieke versie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testtaak Stage</title>
      <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/stage/Testtaak%20Stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 19:18:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/stage/Testtaak%20Stage/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;random-testcode-markdown:1485c913c6901969dbf1bc27a398e5d8&#34;&gt;Random testcode markdown&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;deel 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;deel 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welkom op de GIP/Stage site van Mario Van Kerckhoven</title>
      <link>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/welkom/Welkomstwoord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 19:04:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mario-vankerckhoven.github.io/welkom/Welkomstwoord/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;een-kort-stukje-uitleg:1dda72a6a3583e1c24e1b4ab2830d714&#34;&gt;Een kort stukje uitleg&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;de-icoontjes-in-de-linkerbovenhoek:1dda72a6a3583e1c24e1b4ab2830d714&#34;&gt;De icoontjes in de linkerbovenhoek:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Immalle: Rechtstreekse link naar de website van de school&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook: Laat een like achter voor de school&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;de-icoontjes-in-de-rechterbovenhoek:1dda72a6a3583e1c24e1b4ab2830d714&#34;&gt;De icoontjes in de rechterbovenhoek:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Welkom: Algemene meldingen / korte uitleg hoe de website werkt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stage: Hier worden alle stage opdrachten gepubliceerd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gip: Hier worden alle opdracht in verband met de GIP gepubliceerd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>